<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Quotes</string>
    <string name="persons">Persons</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="About">About this app</string>
    <string name="ST">Special Thanks…</string>
    <string name="Yanndroid">… to Yanndroid, who did not stopped to explain the things to me even if I did not understand much and who always helped me, when I had a problem.</string>
    <string name="RM">You want to contact me or you found an issue?</string>
    <string name="BlackMesa">… to BlackMesa, who helped me to optimize this app.</string>
    <string name="Info">If you found an issue, you can write it on GitHub in \"Issues\" or privately on Telegram.\nIf you want to send me a quote, you can do it on Telegram.</string>
    <string name="QuoteAA1">The wounds you are not seeing, are the most difficult to heal</string>
    <string name="QuoteBF1">Most people die at 25 and aren’t buried until they’re 75.</string>
    <string name="QouteBP1">A drop of love is more than an ocean of mind.</string>
    <string name="QuoteBM1">The good times of today, are the sad thoughts of tomorrow.</string>
    <string name="QuoteBM2">Open your eyes, and look within. Are you satisfied with the life you\'re living?</string>
    <string name="QuoteBM3">The day you stop racing, is the day you win the race.</string>
    <string name="QuoteBM4">Love the life you live. Live the life you love.</string>
    <string name="QuoteCB1">Can you remember who you were before the world told you who you have to be?</string>
    <string name="QuoteCC1">I regret nothing in my life except for the things i didn\'t do</string>
    <string name="QuoteCC2">"If you were born without wings, do nothing to prevent them from growing. "</string>
    <string name="QuoteDP1">"If you don't like the path you're walking, make a new one "</string>
    <string name="QuoteDP2">When someone shows you their true colors, trust them</string>
    <string name="QuoteEH1">You are so brave and quiet I forget you are suffering</string>
    <string name="QuoteFK1">Paths are made by walking them</string>
    <string name="QuotesGA1">All you ever wanted is on the other side of fear</string>
    <string name="QuotesJP1">Maybe there are better times, but this is our time</string>
    <string name="QuotesJWG1">It must come from the heart, what should touch the heart</string>
    <string name="QuotesJWG2">Wer nicht angefangen hat, wird niemals fertig werden</string>
    <string name="QuotesJW1">Don\'t give up on your dreams or your dreams will give you up</string>
    <string name="QuotesJC1">The cage you dare not enter holds the treasure you seek</string>
    <string name="QuotesJ1">Pain is not only seen in tears, sometimes it is hidden behind a smile</string>
    <string name="QuotesJ2">"Many can make you laugh, but just a few can make you happy  "</string>
    <string name="QuoteJB1">Sometimes the heart sees things that are invisible to the eye</string>
    <string name="QuoteK1">It does not matter how slowly you go as long as you do not stop.</string>
    <string name="QuoteLT1">Everyone thinks of changing the world, but no one thinks of changing himself.</string>
    <string name="QuoteLD1">Life is like a coin, you can buy anything with it, but only once</string>
    <string name="QuoteLS1">Character can be seen in even the smallest actions</string>
    <string name="QuoteL1">" Even a journey of a thousand miles begins with a single step"</string>
    <string name="QuoteMA1">You should not fear the death but to never live at all</string>
    <string name="QuotePP1">"Everything you can imagine is real  "</string>
    <string name="QuoteRS1">What would you do if you knew you couldn\'t fail?</string>
    <string name="QuoteU1">Do it or don\'t do it, you\'ll regret both</string>
    <string name="QuoteU2">Broken people have the prettiest smiles because they know what happiness means</string>
    <string name="QuoteU3">It\'s not the things that scare us, it\'s the way we think about them</string>
    <string name="QuoteU4">The worst feeling is when you are at home but feel like you want to go home</string>
    <string name="QuoteU5">Sometimes beautiful things end because people are not ready for them</string>
    <string name="QuoteU6">If you weren\'t ready for it, you wouldn\'t have the opportunity.</string>
    <string name="QuoteU7">The worst kind of sadness is the one you can\'t explain.</string>
    <string name="QuoteU8">Although thoughts weigh nothing, one can collapse under their weight.</string>
    <string name="QuoteU9">Grief isn\'t the opposite of happiness, it\'s a part of it.</string>
    <string name="QuoteU10">Death must be a beautiful journey, because no one has returned yet.</string>
    <string name="QuoteU11">You deserve the love you are trying to give to others all the time.</string>
    <string name="QuoteU12">When I think of you I smile, but my heart hurts like hell</string>
    <string name="QuoteU13">Losing your heart is the best way to discover you have one</string>
    <string name="QuoteU14">It doesn\'t matter who\'s in front of you if you know who stands behind you.</string>
    <string name="QuoteU15">Sometimes nothing happens for a long time, and then everything happens at once</string>
    <string name="QuoteU16">The moment you accept yourself, you become beautiful</string>
    <string name="QuoteU17">Life keeps repeating things until you learn the lesson</string>
    <string name="QuoteU18">What catches your eye shows you what your soul is looking for</string>
    <string name="QuoteU19">I will never apologize for my heart that breaks so easily but loves so strongly</string>
    <string name="QuoteU20">"You can't be happy if what you're holding on to is something that makes you sad  "</string>
    <string name="QuoteU21">You can touch me without touching me</string>
    <string name="QuoteU22">You don\'t build a relationship with people in days, weeks or months, but in moments</string>
    <string name="QuoteWP1">How do you spell love? You don\'t spell it, you feel it</string>
    <string name="QuoteWP2">Some people care too much about you, I guess it\'s called love.</string>
    <string name="QuoteWS1">The whole world is a stage and we are all actors.</string>
    <string name="QuoteWS2">the grief that does not speak  Whispers the o\'er-fraught heart, and bids it break.</string>
</resources>